thismoment.com 2013-09-14

# Privacy Policy

* ## Overview

The application that you are viewing is called the Thismoment Distributed Engagement Channel (“DEC” or the “Service”). The DEC is operated by us, Thismoment, Inc., for our partner whose content and brand are featured in the DEC. The DEC is a multi-media application that enables our partner to tell you about its products, services or special events while also allowing you, the user, to participate in the experience by submitting your own content, such as comments, photos and videos. The DEC may include content from multiple social networks and sites, such as Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, and Flickr. The DEC may appear on the website of one or more of those services, on our partner's site or on other sites.

Because we are offering the Service on behalf of our partner, all information that we collect is made available to our partner whose DEC you are viewing under the terms of this Privacy Policy (e.g., if you are interacting with a DEC for a particular car, the information we collect is made available to that car company). This information may also be made available under the terms of this Privacy Policy to the operator of the website where you interacted with the DEC under the terms of this Privacy Policy (e.g., if you interacted with the DEC on YouTube, the information we collect may be made available to YouTube).

In some cases, the DEC may also include a link to our partner's privacy policy, in which case the information that we collect may also be used under the terms of that policy (e.g., if you are interacting with a DEC for a particular car and a link to the car company's privacy policy is also displayed on the DEC, then the information collected through the DEC is also subject to the car company's privacy policy). This Service is not intended for use by persons under thirteen (13) years of age. Thismoment does not knowingly collect Personal Information from or about children under the age of thirteen (13).

## Information We Collect

We may collect the following kinds of information.

#### INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE

Thismoment collects information from you when you provide it to us, such as when you register for our Service, enter a contest, submit content to the Service (such as a video or photo submission), or communicate with us, such as through email or SMS. The information you provide us may include information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information” or “PII”), such as your name, your email address, your phone number or your mailing address. See the section below called “Public Activity” about information that you submit to public areas of the Service. 

#### INFORMATION FROM SERVICES THAT YOU USE TO CONNECT TO OUR SERVICES

We may also receive information about you from the service that you used to connect to our Service (e.g., if you use your account with Facebook, YouTube or Twitter to log into our Service). This information is described in the privacy policy for that service or in the permissions message that you receive when connecting through that service. It can include your name, your user name on that service, your email, information about your friends on that service and information about the activity of you and your friends on that service or on our Service. Please review the privacy policies of any service that you use to connect to our Service as well as any permissions notice that you get during the connection process.

#### INFORMATION FROM COOKIES AND SIMILAR DEVICES 

Cookies are data that we place on a user's browser that allow us to know how often someone visits a site and the activities they conduct while using the Service (such as the pages visited, links clicked on, videos viewed, commenting activity, contest voting, etc.). Every computer is assigned a different cookie by Thismoment. [Click here](https://www.thismoment.com/privacy/eucookies) for more information about how Thismoment uses cookies.

#### INFORMATION FROM MOBILE DEVICES

If you are interacting with our service on a mobile device, we may receive your device and hardware ID, device type, carrier, carrier user ID, the content of your request and basic usage statistics about your device and usage of our Service. If you use location-related aspects of our Service, we may also receive information about your actual location. If you provide it to us or send us a message from your mobile device, we may also collect your phone number. Your device may also store information about your usage of our Service. Please consult your device documentation on how to manage local storage.

#### INFORMATION BASED ON STANDARD WEB PROTOCOLS

When you access our Service through a browser, application or other client, like other web providers, our servers automatically record certain information. This data is recorded in server logs and may include information such as your web request, your interaction with the Service, the website that you were visiting when you came to our Service, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and language, the date and time of your request, and your cookie data.

#### INFORMATION FROM THIRD-PARTY APPLICATIONS

Some of our DECs include third-party applications, which have their own privacy policies that govern their collection of information. Any information received by Thismoment form those third-party applications will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### ANALYTICS TECHNOLOGIES

We use third party service providers to help us collect, report and analyze information about how users interact with our Service. These providers include Google Analytics [(see privacy policy)](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html) and Omniture [(see privacy policy)](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/product).

#### INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES

This Privacy Policy only applies to Thismoment's Services. It does not apply to, and we do not have control over, the sites on which our Services are distributed or products, services or sites that are linked to from within our Service. These sites may place cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. We may also display advertisements on our sites, and in the course of serving the ads, some advertisers and their ad serving partners may place cookies on your computer or may recognize and collect data based on a cookie previously placed on your computer. We do not have access to or control over the data or cookies of these third parties. [Click here](https://www.thismoment.com/privacy/eucookies) for more information about how Thismoment uses cookies.

#### PUBLIC ACTIVITIES

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any public activity on the Service. Public activity is any activity that is visible to other users, such as posting a comment, entering a submission in a contest, or uploading a video or photo. Any information that you submit as part of any public activity, including your name, user name or photo, becomes public. Public information may be used by Thismoment and the partner on whose behalf Thismoment is offering the Service for any online or offline promotional or commercial usage, in any and all media. It is also visible to, and may be used by, any other user of the Service. Thismoment has no obligation to remove any information that you have made available through public activity. You should think carefully before disclosing any personal information in any online public environment.

#### INFORMATION USAGE

Here are the ways that we use the information that we collect in connection with your usage of the Service: 

  * \- to provide our Services to you and develop new services;
  * \- to perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses, including to determine:
    * \- how users interact with our Service; 
    * \- the success of a campaign or promotion being offered by our Partner; 
    * \- the level of interest in our Partner's products or Services; 
  * \- to customize the products and services we offer to you and to allow advertising to be served to users based on what we think is most relevant or interesting to them; 
  * \- to contact you in connection with a contest or sweepstakes or if you have requested to receive information from us or our partner; 
  * \- to protect the rights, safety or property of Thismoment, our partners and our users. 

#### SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

This section sets forth the circumstances in which Thismoment may share your Personal Information with a third party. As mentioned above, Thismoment is providing the Service on behalf of the partner whose branding and content are featured in the DEC, and as such acts as a data processor for its partner. Accordingly, all information gathered in connection with your usage of that partner's DEC, including your Personal Information, will be provided to that partner for use in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition, this information may also be provided to the website through which you are accessing the Service (e.g., Facebook or YouTube). Our partner may also display its own privacy policy through the DEC, in which case our partner may also use the data in any manner permitted by that privacy policy.

We also contract with other companies to provide services on our behalf, such as web hosting services, application development, analytics, security, and data processing. These companies are obligated to maintain the confidentiality of the Personal Information and are restricted from using it for any purpose that is incompatible with the uses set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

We may disclose Personal Information to our corporate subsidiaries or affiliates. Any Personal Information provided to Thismoment's subsidiaries or affiliates will be treated in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may provide Personal Information about you where we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government requirement; (b) enforce any applicable terms of service, (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Thismoment, its partners, its users or the public.

If Thismoment undergoes any merger or sale of its stock or some or all of its assets, we may transfer your Personal Information to the successor entity so long as it continues to maintain that information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which it was collected.

Other than as described in the preceding paragraphs, Thismoment will not (a) sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your Personal Information or (b) use your Personal Information for any purpose other than those described in this Privacy Policy, without your consent. 

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes to this policy will be posted at this URL: Thismoment/privacy. We will not use data we collect in a manner that is materially different from promises made in the version of the Privacy Policy under which it was collected without your consent.

#### UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can contact us by emailing us at support@thismoment.com and we will make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information in order to correct, amend or delete it unless prohibited by law. We may decline to process requests if it would require effort disproportionate to the privacy risk, would violate the rights of others or would prejudice an ongoing legal proceeding or investigation. Because of the way we make back-up copies of our data, residual copies of the information may remain in our backup systems. We also may not be able to delete Personal Information that you have submitted through public activities, and even after removal and it may remain viewable in cached and archived locations or on other websites not within our control. We may charge a reasonable fee to access your Personal Information if to do so would require disproportionate effort. Updating or deletion of your Personal Information will not have any effect on other information that Thismoment maintains.

#### SECURITY

We recognize that security is important and take reasonable measures to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alternation or destruction. If you believe that the Personal Information you have provided us has been compromised, or if you become aware of a potential security vulnerability in our Service, please contact us at privacy@thismoment.com.

#### COMMENTS AND QUESTIONS

Thismoment periodically reviews its privacy practices and this Privacy Policy. We encourage interested persons to raise any concerns using the contact information provided below and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any concerns or complaints.

Email: privacy@Thismoment.com

Mail: Customer Service, Thismoment, Inc., 222 Kearny Street, Suite 500, San Francisco, CA 94108

Phone: +1-415-200-4730 

#### NON-U.S. USERS; SAFE HARBOR

Thismoment is hosted and operated in the United States and is subject to United States law. Any personal information that you provide to us is being provided to us in the United States and will be hosted on United States servers. You consent to the transfer of your personal information to the United States. If you are accessing Thismoment from outside the United States, please be advised that United States law may not offer the same privacy protections as the law of your jurisdiction. Thismoment has certified that it abides by the Safe Harbor Principles developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, storage, use, transfer and other processing of Consumer Personal Data transferred from the European Economic Area or Switzerland to the United States (the “Safe Harbor Principles”). To view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's [website](http://export.gov/safeharbor/).

If you have a complaint about our usage of Personal Information, please contact us at the address provided above under “Comments and Questions.” We will investigate and take steps to remedy any violation of the Safe Harbor Principles. If a complaint or dispute under the Safe Harbor Principles cannot be resolved through our internal process, Thismoment has agreed to cooperate with the [European Union Data Protection Authorities](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/eu/index_en.htm) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner. 

Last updated: October 2012
